More than a movie. It's a celebration.
That's Entertainment! is a documentary, family,
music film directed by Jack Haley Jr..
Various MGM stars from yesterday present their favorite
musical moments from the studio's 50 year history.
Self - Host / Narrator, played by Fred Astaire.
Self - Host / Narrator, played by Bing Crosby.
Self - Host / Narrator, played by Gene Kelly.
Self - Host / Narrator, played by Peter Lawford.
Self - Host / Narrator, played by Liza Minnelli.
Self - Host / Narrator, played by Donald O'Connor.
That's Entertainment!
is a 1974 American compilation film released by
Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer to celebrate the studio's  50th anniversary.
The success of the retrospective prompted a 1976 sequel, the related 1985
film That's Dancing!, and a third installment in 1994.
MCA Records released a soundtrack of the music in the film in 1974.